http://www.jiskha.com/legal/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
Jiskha Homework Help takes privacy very seriously. We collect non-sensitive information from anonymous visitors. With permission, we collect additional information about registered users of our website. The following privacy policy has been written in order to clearly and specifically identify what information we collect. If you have any questions or concerns regarding our privacy policy, please contact us.
Jiskha Homework Help is abbreviated as "we" and "us" in the following privacy policy.
Collection of Data from All Visitors
We collect IP addresses of all visitors, the first name of visitors who post messages to our bulletin board, email addresses of those who communicate with us via email, and aggregate information on what pages visitors access or visit.
Collection of Data from Registered Users
Registered users MUST be of age 13 or older to create and maintain an account on Jiskha.com. We collect and make public the following fields from all registered users:
username
display name (usually a formatted verion of the username)
gender
account creation date
We also collect but keep private the following fields from all registered users:
birthday
How We Use Collected Data
Information we collect is used to improve the user experience for individual visitors, improve our entire website for all visitors, and respond more efficiently to customer service requests. Information we collect is never shared with external entities, and information we collect is never sold to external companies.
We use internet cookies to store user preferences for future visits.
Visitor Contact Information
If you supply us with contact information (email address, postal address, telephone number), you will only receive the information that you asked for.
Advertisements
We enable third-party vendors to place ads in various areas of our website. These vendors may use non-personally identifiable information to serve relevant ads based on a user's previous visits to our website and other websites on the internet. To learn more about this practice or to opt-out of this method of advertising, please visit https://www.networkadvertising.org/.
Third-party advertisers, such as Google AdSense, have separate and independent privacy policies, and we have no responsibility or liability for the content or activities of these sites.
Stored Information
Upon request, we provide site visitors with access to all information that we maintain about them. Visitors may also request to have any inaccuracies corrected in the information we stored about them.
Security
We always use industry-standard encryption technologies when transferring data to and from our website. When we transfer and receive certain types of sensitive information such as financial or health information, we redirect visitors to a secure server that uses an SSL certificate. We have appropriate security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse, or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our website.
Updates to Our Privacy Policy
From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change in the future, we will contact you before we use your data for these new purposes to notify you of the policy change and to provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. Changes will also be posted to our website to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our website periodically.
Conclusion
Thank you for taking the time to read this privacy policy. Jiskha Homework Help intends to abide by this policy at all times.
Ask a New Question
